Finding Aid for Gunnar Birkerts and Associates, 1960-2014
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- St. Peter's Lutheran Church, Columbus, Indiana 1981-1988, 997 drawings; 3 linear feet
  - St. Peter's Lutheran Church Drawings
    - Shop Drawings
      - Representative Drawings. Blue-line prints with notations in red ink
        - Upper Level Shoring Layout and Section by The Burke Company. 02/20/1987 (Map-case 31, Folder 41)
        - Church Steeple Framing and Cladding Plans, Elevations, Sections and Details by Orman O. McKinley Co., Inc. Seven prints 2/86-7/87 (Map-case 31, Folder 41)
        - Steeple Bell Plan and Section by Force Design, Inc. 6/87 (Map-case 31, Folder 41)
        - Millwork Plans, Elevations, Sections and Details by Anderson Wood Products Company. Three prints 6/87 (Map-case 31, Folder 41)
        - Pew, Pulpit, Communion Rail, Communion Cart, Modesty Screen, Registry, Candle Holders and Kneelers Plans, Elevations and Sections by Garnett Church Furnishings. Eight prints, 5/87-2/88.01 (Map-case 31, Folder 41)
        - Stonework Plans, Elevations, Sections and Details by Woolery Stone Co., Inc. 01/28/1988 (Map-case 31, Folder 41)
- Additional Projects' Records and Drawings
  A 2008 addendum to the collection includes records and drawings associated with 74 more projects of Gunnar Birkerts and Associates, encompassing an additional 3,000 drawings and 13 linear feet of textual materials and photographs. Unlike the 14 buildings in the original collection, which are documented from the beginning of the design process to the end, this second accession of projects includes only original, ink-on-vellum, presentation drawings and/or construction photographs for 53 of the 74 buildings. However, the beauty and clarity of these visual materials enrich our appreciation for the evolution, breadth and genius of Birkerts' work over fifty years.
  Twenty-one of the additional projects in this series are documented more fully with textual records and construction drawings. These buildings are:
  Bald Mountain Recreational Facility, Pontiac, MI (1964-1969)
  Contemporary Arts Museum, Houston, TX (1970-1972)
  Cornell University Uris Library Addition, Ithaca, NY (1980-1982)
  Detroit Institute of Arts, South Wing Addition (1964)
  Duke University Law School Addition, Durham, NC (1989-1995)
  Fisher Administrative Center, University of Detroit (1964-1966)
  Holtzman & Silverman Office Building, Southfield, MI (1983-1990)
  I.B.M Information Systems Facility, Sterling Forest, NY (1968-1984)
  I.B.M. Office Building, Southfield, MI (1975-1995)
  Kemper Museum of Contemporary Art & Design, Kansas City, MO (1991-1994)
  Lillibridge Elementary School Addition, Detroit, MI (1962-1963)
  Livonia Public Library, New South Branch, Livonia, MI (1065-1967
  Marathon Oil Office Building, Detroit, MI (1962-1964)
  Oberlin College Conservatory of Music Library Addition, Oberlin, OH (1986-88)
  Ohio State University Law Building Addition, Columbus, OH (1988-1993)
  St. Bede's Church, Southfield, MI (1966-1969)
  Subterranean Urban Systems Study (1974)
  United States Embassy Building, Helsinki, Finland (1975)
  University of California at San Diego Central Library Addition (1987-1993)
  University of Iowa College of Law Building, Iowa City (1979-1986)
  Vocational Technical Institute Campus Master Plan, Southern Illinois University, Carterville, IL (1967-1971)
  The textual records associated with the above twenty-one projects are comprised of Birkerts' conceptual statements about each, written specifications, and memoranda and bulletins, which describe the construction process. The documentation of these buildings is further enriched by visual materials, including construction photographs and slides and contract drawings. In addition to the working drawings, schematic design, design development and presentation drawings are also available for a few of them. The seventy-four projects in this series are described in alphabetical order in the finding aid.
  The "Additional Projects" series also contains the drawings of a few projects by Eero Saarinen's and Minoru Yamasaki's firms, both of which employed Gunnar Birkerts as a young architect in the 1950s. Mr. Birkerts included these materials in his donation to the Bentley Library. These construction drawings are all prints of originals and document projects completed by the Saarinen and Yamasaki while Birkerts received training in their firms. Three buildings by Eeero Saarinen and Associates and nine buildings by Yamasaki are included in this collection.
  - Albion Church (Grace Lutheran Church), Albion, Michigan 1960
    - Architectural Drawings
      - Presentation Drawings undated, ink-on-vellum drawings and one pencil-on-vellum rendering by Keith Brown) (Tube 1)
  - Amman, Jordan, Housing Competition 1976
    - Architectural Drawings
      - Presentation Drawings undated, ink and pencil drawings on vellum (Tube 2)
  - Amsterdam City Hall Competition 1968
    - Architectural Drawings
      - Presentation Drawings undated, ink and pencil drawings on vellum and on one sepia print (Tube 3)
  - Anchorage Library Competition, Anchorage, Alaska 1981
    - Architectural Drawings
      - Presentation Drawings undated, pencil and ink drawings on tracing paper and vellum and sepia prints (Tube 4)
  - Bald Mountain Recreational Facility, Pontiac, Michigan 1964-1969
    - Architectural Records
      - Architect's Conceptual Statement (Box 70)
      - Contract Documents and General Specifications 3/28/1968 & 5/1/1969 (Box 70)
      - Memoranda, 7/2/1968-11/26/1969 (Box 70)
      - Progress Meeting Minutes, 4/17/1964-3/5/1969 (Box 70)
      - Photographs undated, 26 photographs color and black and white 3-1/4x4-1/4-inch (Box 70)
    - Architectural Drawings
      - Presentation Drawings undated, ink and pencil drawings on vellum (Tube 5)
      - Construction Drawings 1/26/1968, blue-line prints with pencil notations
        - Architectural Drawings (A-1 to A-10) (Tube 6)
        - Mechanical/Electrical Drawings (ME-1 to 6 and E-2 to E-4) (Tube 6)
        - Supplementary Construction Drawings 3/10/1969, blueprints (Tube 6)
  - Baldwin Public Library Addition, Birmingham, Michigan 1980-1983
    - Architectural Drawings
      - Presentation Drawings undated, ink-on-vellum drawing, blue-line prints and electrostatic prints on mylar (Tube 7)
  - Camp Wildflecken Chapel and Educational Facility, U. S. Army, Germany 1980-1983
    - Architectural Drawings
      - Presentation Drawings undated, pencil and ink drawings on vellum and tracing paper (Tube 8)
  - Church of the Servant, Kentwood, Michigan 1988-1994
    - Architectural Records
      - Construction Photographs 1993, 170 prints color 3-1/2 x 5 and 4 x 6-inch; 64 slides color (Box 81)
  - J. A. Citrin Sons Company Office Building, Bingham Farms, Michigan 1979
    - Architectural Drawings
      - Presentation Drawings undated, ink-on-vellum drawings (Tube 9)
  - Computer Work Station
    - Architectural Drawing
      - Presentation Drawing undated, ink-on-vellum drawing (Tube 10)
  - Contemporary Arts Museum, Houston, Texas 1970-1972
    - Architectural Records
      - Architect's Conceptual Statement (Box 71)
      - Outline Specifications 6/10/1970 (Box 71)
      - Specifications for General Contract, 10/2/1970, 2 folders (Box 71)
      - Addenda # 1 & 2 10/9/1970-10/20/1970 (Box 71)
      - Pre-Contract Bulletins # 1 & 2, 2/2/1971-2/19/1971 (Box 71)
      - Bulletins # 1-7, 8/16/1971-3/2/1972 (Box 71)
      - Memoranda
        - #1-20 1/19/1970-2/18/1971 (Box 71)
        - #21-59 2/25/1971-2/15/1973 (Box 71)
      - Extra Services Memoranda #1-7 6/12/1972-10/30/1972 (Box 71)
      - Construction Photographs, 5/1/1971-3/1972, 233 slides color (Box 71)
      - Photographs of Finished Building 3/1972, 2 prints black and white 8x10-inch (Box 71)
      - Exterior and Interior Photographs December 1991, 55 prints color 4 x 6-inch (Box 71)
      - Newspaper and Journal Articles 1969-1997 (Box 71)
    - Architectural Drawings
      - Presentation Drawings undated, ink-on-vellum drawings (Tube 11)
      - Construction Drawings 10/02/1970, pencil drawings on vellum and sepia prints (Tube 12)
        - Architectural Drawings (A-1 to A-18), revised 11/8/1971 (Tube 12)
        - Structural Drawings by Robert M. Darvas and Associates (S-1 to S-8) (Tube 12)
        - Mechanical/Electrical Drawings (1 to 6, E-1 to E-5) by Hoyem Associates, Inc. undated (Tube 12)
        - Supplemental Construction Details 6/1967-1/1973, 10 drawings pencil drawings on vellum and sepia;blue-line prints (Tube 12)
  - Cornell University Uris Library Addition, Ithaca, New York 1980-1982
    - Architectural Records
      - Architect's Conceptual Statement (Box 73)
      - Specifications for General Contract 3/1/1981
        - Division #1 (Box 73)
        - Divisions #2-6 (Box 73)
        - Divisions #7-12 (Box 73)
        - Divisions #14-16 (Box 73)
        - Structural Drawing Book 3/2/1981 (Box 73)
      - Addenda #1-3 and to Structural Drawing Book 3/10/1981-5/13/1981 (Box 73)
      - Original Sketches: Proposal Requests, Clarifications, Field Orders 12/1981-7/1982 (Box 73)
      - Bulletins & Proposal Requests #1-19 6/26/1981-8/27/1982 (Box 73)
      - Memoranda
        - #1-35 8/15/1980-12/11/1981 (Box 73)
        - #36-64, 1/8/1982-10/22/1982 (Box 73)
      - Construction Photographs undated, 36 prints color 3 x 4-inch (Box 73)
      - Construction Photographs 1981-1982, 58 slides color (Box 73)
      - Newspaper Articles 1980 (Box 73)
    - Architectural Drawings
      - Presentation Drawings undated, ink-on-vellum drawings (Tube 13)
      - Construction Drawings, pencil drawings on mylar (Tube 14)
        - Architectural Drawings (A-1 to A-32) 3/1/1981 revised 05/12/1982 (Tube 14)
        - Supplementary Construction Drawings 10/2/1981-5/25/1982 (Tube 14)
        - Structural Drawings by Skilling, Helle, Christiansen, Robertson, PLC, Structural Engineers (S-1 to S-5) 3/2/1981 revised 5/18/1981, electrostatic prints on mylar (Tube 15)
        - Mechanical/Electrical Drawings by Kunstadt Associates, PC, Mechanical & Electrical Engineers (E-1 to E-6, P-1 to P-4, H-1 to H-8) 3/1/1981 revised 5/18/1981, electrostatic prints on mylar (Tube 15)
  - Corning Bus Shelter, Corning, New York
    - Architectural Drawings
      - Presentation Drawings undated, ink-on-vellum drawings (Tube 16)
  - Corning Public Library I & II, Corning, New York 1969
    - Architectural Drawings
      - Presentation Drawings undated, ink and pencil drawings on vellum (Tube 17)
  - Detroit Institute of Arts-South Wing Addition 1964
    - Architectural Records
      - Outdoor Sign Specifications and Correspondence 1963-1964 (Box 70)
      - Newspaper Articles 1964-1989 (Box 70)
    - Architectural Drawings
      - Original Building Construction Drawings by Paul P. Cret, Zantzinger, Borie & Medary, Philadelphia (3 to 28) 7/1924, blue-line prints (Tube 18)
      - Schematic Design Sketches and Drawings by Gunnar Birkerts undated, pencil and crayon drawings on tracing paper (Tube 19)
      - Presentation Drawings and Facade Studies undated, pencil-on-vellum drawings (Tube 20)
        (two by Harold Van Dine)
      - Construction Drawings by Harley, Ellington, Cowin and Stirton, Inc., Gunnar Birkerts, Design Consultant 9/26/1963, blueprints (Tube 21)
        - Architectural Drawings (A1-1 to A4-28) (Tube 21)
        - Architectural Drawings (A5-1 to A7-11) (Tube 22)
        - Structural and Mechanical Drawings (S-1 to S-10, 2 to 20) (Tube 23)
        - Electrical Drawings (E-1 to E-17) (Tube 24)
  - Detroit People Mover Elevated Guideway, Detroit, Michigan
    - Architectural Drawings
      - Presentation Drawings undated, ink-on-vellum drawings (Tube 25)
  - Domino's Pizza, Inc., Headquarters, Chairman's Suite Stained Glass 1988
    - Architectural Drawings
      - Presentation Drawings undated, pencil-on vellum drawings and blue-line print (Tube 26)
  - Domino's Pizza, Inc., Headquarters, Domino's Farms, Ann Arbor, Michigan 1984-1998
    - Architectural Records
      - Construction Photographs 1985-1987, 20 slides color (Box 82)
    - Architectural Drawings
      - Presentation Drawings undated, ink-on-vellum drawings and two ink drawings on blue-line prints by Gunnar Birkerts (Tube 27)
      - Presentation Drawings undated, ink-on-vellum drawings and two ink drawings on blue-line prints by Gunnar Birkerts (Tube 28)
        (continued)
      - Presentation Drawings undated, ink-on-vellum drawings and two ink drawings on blue-line prints by Gunnar Birkerts (Tube 29)
  - Domino's Pizza, Inc., Tower, Domino's Farms, Ann Arbor, Michigan 1987-1988
    - Architectural Drawings
      - Presentation Drawings undated, ink drawings on vellum and mylar (Tube 30)
  - Drummond Island Residence, Drummond Island, Michigan
    - Architectural Drawings
      - Presentation Drawings undated, ink-on-mylar drawings (Tube 31)
  - Duke University Law School Addition, Durham, North Carolina 1989-1995
    - Architectural Records
      - Construction Photographs 1994, 77 slides color (Box 77)
      - Newspaper Article 1995 (Box 77)
    - Architectural Drawings
      - Design Development Drawings (Tube 32)
        - Presentation Drawings of Elevations by William Hartman 9/11/1990, 2 prints (Tube 32)
        - 60% Document Review Set (A-305, A-603 to A-609, A-701 to A-710, A-806), 11/8/1990, pencil drawings on tracing paper, vellum and electrostatic prints, taped to blue-line prints (Tube 32)
  - Elmwood Park Redevelopment Competition, Detroit, Michigan 1964
    - Architectural Drawings
      - Presentation Drawings undated, ink and pencil drawings on vellum and electrostatic prints on mylar (Tube 33)
  - Federated Department Stores Office Building, Cincinnati, Ohio 1977
    - Architectural Drawings
      - Presentation Drawings undated, ink-on-vellum drawings (Tube 34)
  - Fisher Administrative Center, University of Detroit, Michigan 1964-1966
    - Architectural Records
      - Architect's Conceptual Statement (Box 70)
      - Design Notebook undated (Box 70)
      - Specifications for General Contract 11/16/1964
        - Sections #1-6 (Box 70)
        - Sections #7-16 (Box 70)
      - Bulletins #1-8 1/25/1965-6/25/1966 (Box 70)
      - Memoranda
        - 1964-1965 (Box 70)
        - 1966-1967 (Box 70)
      - Photographs of Building Model undated, 3 photocopies black and white 10x13-inch (Box 70)
      - Photographs of Drawings undated, 7 photocopies black and white 10x13-inch (Box 70)
      - Construction Photographs 1965, 36 slides color (Box 70)
      - Newspaper Articles 1964-1967 (Box 70)
    - Architectural Drawings
      - Presentation Drawings, two dated 7/21//1964, pencil and ink drawings on vellum, linen and sepia print (Tube 35)
      - Construction Drawings 11/16/1964 revised 7/30/1965, pencil-on-vellum drawings (Tube 36)
        - Architectural Drawings (A0-1 to A8-3) (Tube 36)
        - Mechanical and Electrical Drawings by E. G. Siegel, Consulting Mechanical & Electrical Engineers (M-1 to M-16 and E-1 to E-9) (Tube 36)
        - Supplementary Construction Drawings 11/16/1964-3/30/1966, pencil-on-vellum drawings and sepia prints (Tube 36)
      - Structural Drawings by Holforty, Widrig, O'Neill & Levin Associates, Inc., Consulting Engineers, (S-1 to S-7) 11/16/1964 revised 1/25/1965, blueprints (Tube 37)
  - Ford Motor Company Pavilion for Hemisfair '68, San Antonio, Texas 1967-1968
    - Architectural Drawings
      - Presentation Drawings undated, ink and pencil drawings on vellum (Tube 38)
  - Ford Motor Company Visitor Reception Center, Dearborn, Michigan 1971-1974
    - Architectural Records
      - Construction Photographs of Scheme No. 2 1973-1974, 27 slides color (Box 82)
    - Architectural Drawings
      - Presentation Drawings undated, ink-on-vellum drawings (Tube 39)
  - Glen Oaks Community College, Centreville, Michigan 1966-1971
    - Architectural Drawings
      - Presentation Drawings undated, ink drawings on linen and vellum and two pencil-on-vellum renderings by Chris Hanson (Tube 40)
  - Holtzman & Silverman Office Building, Southfield, Michigan 1983-1990
    - Architectural Records
      - Architect's Conceptual Statement (Box 77)
      - Specifications 7/15/1987
        - Divisions # 5-7 (Box 77)
        - Divisions #8-14 (Box 77)
        - Divisions #15-16 (Box 77)
      - Bulletins # 1-5 10/16/1987-8/22/1988 (Box 77)
      - Memoranda #1-25 9/27/1983-4/30/1986 (Box 77)
      - Memoranda #26-93 5/12/1986-8/29/1988 (Box 77)
      - Memoranda #94-140, 8/31/1988-6/8/1992 (Box 77)
      - Newspaper Articles 1991-1992 (Box 77)
      - Construction Photographs 10/28/1987-5/2/1990, 236 prints color 3-1/2x5-1/2 and 4x6-inch (Box 77)
    - Architectural Drawings
      - Presentation Drawings undated, pencil drawings on tracing paper and blue-line prints with pantone overlays (Tube 41)
      - Architectural Construction Drawings (A-1 to A-16) 7/15/1988 revised 7/15/1988, electrostatic prints on mylar (Tube 42)
      - Structural Construction Drawings by Robert Darvas Associates, Structural Engineers (S-1 to S-3) 7/15/1987 revised 2/2/1988, electrostatic prints on mylar (Tube 42)
      - Mechanical/Electrical Drawings by Professional Consultants Incorporated, Mechanical & Electrical Engineers (M-1 to M-5, E-1 to E-2) 7/15/1987 revised 7/15/1988, pencil drawings on electrostatic prints on mylar (Tube 42)
      - Interiors Construction Drawings (A-0 to A-20) 6/14/1988-11/18/1988, pencil drawings on vellum and mylar and electrostatic prints (Tube 43)
      - Landscape Construction Drawings by David R. Jackson 4/23/1989, 10/10/1989, 2 drawings blue-line prints (Tube 43)
  - International Business Machines Corporation Management Information Systems Facility, Sterling Forest, NY 1968-1984
    - Architectural Records
      - Architect's Conceptual Statement (Box 78)
      - Building Site Evaluation Study 2/24/1968 (Box 78)
      - Site Utilization Study 5/19/1969 (Box 78)
      - Preliminary Concept, Part 1 7/1/1969 (Box 78)
      - Preliminary Concept, Part 2 8/18/1969 (Box 78)
      - Final Concept Submittable 10/10/1969 (Box 78)
      - Specifications for General Contract 1/30/1970
        - Contract Documents and Sections # 1-2 (Box 78)
        - Sections # 3-11 (Box 78)
        - Sections # 13-16 (Box 78)
      - Structural Drawing Book by Skilling, Helle, Christiansen, Robertson, Structural & Civil Engineers 01/30/1970 (Box 78)
      - Addenda # 1-3 2/11/1970-2/23/1970 (Box 78)
      - Bulletins
        - # 1-15 4/20/1970-12/15/1970 (Box 78)
        - # 16-34 11/2/1970-5/16/1972 (Box 78)
      - Memoranda
        - # 1-50, 5/2/1969-12/18/1969 (Box 78)
        - # 51-100 12/18/1969-2/10/1971 (Box 78)
        - # 101-154, 2/15/1971-1/9/1973 (Box 78)
      - Interiors Memoranda # 1-10 6/10/1974-2/18/1975 (Box 78)
      - Construction Photographs by Haddad Studio Photographers and H. Bernstein Assoc. 12/10/1969-3/15/1972, 2 folders of 110 and 74 prints black and white 8x10-inch; 3x5-inch (Box 79)
      - Specifications for Renovation Construction 10/29/1984 (Box 79)
    - Architectural Drawings
      - Presentation Drawing undated, ink-on-vellum drawing (Tube 44)
      - Construction Drawings
        - Architectural Drawings (A-1 to A-47) 1/30/1970 revised 1/18/1972, pencil drawings on linen (Tube 44)
        - Structural Drawings by Skilling, Helle, Christiansen & Robertson, Structural Engineers (S-1 to S-6) 1/30/1970 revised 10/8/1970, pencil-on-linen drawings (Tube 45)
        - Mechanical and Electrical Drawings by Hoyem, Basso, Adams & Martin, Mechanical Engineers (M-1 to M-21, MEL-2, El-1 to El-18 1/30/1970 revised 9/28/1970, blue-line prints (Tube 45)
        - Renovation Architectural Drawings (A-1 to A-4) 12/10/1984, pencil-on-mylar drawings (Tube 46)
  - International Business Machines Corporation Office Building, Southfield, Michigan 1975-1995
    - Architectural Records for Office Building
      - Architect's Conceptual Statement (Box 79)
      - Site Utilization Study 2/3/1975 (Box 79)
      - Preliminary Concept Submittals I and I 4/18/1975 (Box 79)
      - Final Concept Submittable 6/12/1975 (Box 79)
      - Specifications for General Contract, 12/1/1975
        - Bid and Contract Documents (Box 79)
        - Divisions # 1-2 (Box 79)
        - Divisions # 3-7 (Box 79)
        - Divisions # 8-11 (Box 79)
        - Divisions # 14-15 (Box 79)
        - Division # 16 (Box 79)
      - Structural Drawing Book by Skilling, Helle, Christiansen, Robertson, Structural Engineers, 12/1/1975 (Box 79)
      - Addenda # 1-7 12/16/1975-1/8/1976 (Box 79)
      - Memoranda
        - # 1-75, 12/23/1974-10/8/1975 (Box 79)
        - # 76-150 10/14/1975-12/23/1976 (Box 79)
        - # 151-217, 1/5/1977-2/29/1979 (Box 79)
      - Memoranda (cont.) (Box 80)
        - # 218-241, 3/5/1979-7/18/1980 (Box 80)
      - Interiors Memoranda # 1-22 7/27/1976-4/25/1980 (Box 80)
      - Bulletins
        - # 1-2 3/10/1976-3/24/1976 (Box 80)
        - # 3-3R, 5/14/1976-6/8/1976 (Box 80)
        - # 5-5A 12/10/1976-11/18/1977 (Box 80)
        - # 6-F15, 6/1/1976-8/18/1978 (Box 80)
        - # 16-36 5/27/1977-3/15/1979 (Box 80)
      - Statement of Requirements and Building Provisions Report 10/12/1977 (Box 80)
      - Construction Photographs by Win Brunner Photographer 5/4/1976-3/2/1979, 3 folders of 138 prints black and white 8 x 10-inch (Box 80)
      - Construction Photographs 1977-1978, 86 slides color (Box 80)
      - "Restoration of Wind Damage to the Curtain Wall and Remediation of Panels to Reduce Risk of Future Wind Damage" by Gordon H. Smith Corporation 1/17/1992, 2 volumes (Box 80)
      - Wind Damage Survey by Gunnar Birkerts and Associates, Inc. 3/1992 (Box 80)
      - Specifications for Curtainwall Wind Damage Repair 9/1992 (Box 80)
      - Memoranda for Curtainwall Repair # 1-23, 4/16/1992-2/3/1994 (Box 80)
      - "Wind Damage Repair Specification for Facade Cleaning and Restoration" by Gordon H. Smith Corporation 6/15/1995 (Box 80)
      - Newspaper and Journal Articles 1979-2005 (Box 80)
    - Architectural Records for Southfield Centre Renovation
      - Specifications, Phase I 3/25/1986 (Box 81)
      - Specifications, Phase II 2/20/1987 (Box 81)
      - Specifications, Phase III 3/17/1989 (Box 81)
      - Phases I and II Addenda 3/28/1986-3/19/1987 (Box 81)
      - Revised Drawings 1986-1988 (Box 81)
      - Memoranda
        - # 1-50 12/28/1984-5/18/1985 (Box 81)
        - # 51-100, 5/14/1985-4/3/1986 (Box 81)
        - # 101-150 4/15/1986-8/29/1986 (Box 81)
        - # 151-200, 9/4/1986-3/27/1987 (Box 81)
        - # 201-279, 4/7/1987-8/22/1989 (Box 81)
      - Art Program 1986 (Box 81)
      - Earth Station Specifications and Memoranda 1983-1988 (Box 81)
    - Architectural Drawings for Office Building
      - Presentation Drawings, one dated 7/24/1984, ink drawings on vellum and mylar with pantone and dot screen overlays and blue-line prints with pantone overlays (Tube 47)
      - Construction Drawings (Tube 48)
        - Architectural Drawings (A-2 to A-40), 12/1/1975 revised 12/31/1975, sepia and blue-line prints (Tube 48)
        - Structural Drawings by Skilling, Helle, Christiansen, Robertson, Structural Engineers (S1-1 to S1-8, S2-1 to S2-2), 12/1/1975 revised 10/21/1976, blue-line prints (Tube 49)
        - Site Mechanical Drawings by Joseph R. Loring & Associates, Site, Mechanical, Electrical Engineers (C-1 to C-12), 12/1/1975 revised 10/16/1978, blue-line prints (Tube 49)
        - Mechanical Drawings by Joseph R. Loring & Associates, Site, Mechanical, Electrical Engineers (P-1 to P-9, FP-1 to FP-5, ME-1 to M-17), 12/1/1975 revised 4/14/1978, blue-line and electrostatic prints (Tube 50)
        - Electrical Drawings by Joseph R. Loring & Associates, Site, Mechanical, Electrical Engineers
          - (E-1 to E-35), 12/1/1975 revised 11/20/1978, blue-line, sepia and electrostatic prints (Tube 50)